Midtown Galleries
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Exhibitions, 1932-1982, undated, Series 2:; (4 linear feet)
  - Schedules and General Correspondence, 1932-1982, undated, 2.1:
    This subseries contains exhibition schedules; general information about cooperative exhibitions; and files for seasons of traveling shows which contain schedules, price lists, shipping information, and general correspondence.
    - Exhibition Schedules, 1938/1939-1958/1959 (Reel 5400, Frame 839-859)
    - Cooperative Exhibitions, 1932-1933 (Reel 5400, Frame 860-871)
    - Traveling Shows (removed from loose leaf notebook, original collation retained), 1944-1947, 1955-1968 (Reel 5400, Frame 872-1100)
    - Traveling Shows, 1935/1936-1975, 1982, undated (Reel 5400, Frame 1102-1533)
    - Traveling Shows, cont., 1935/1936-1975, 1982, undated (Reel 5401, Frame 5-812)
  - Midtown Galleries Exhibition Files, A-Z, 1934-1982, undated, 2.2:
    - American Printmakers Exhibitions, 1936-1939 (Reel 5401, Frame 813-896)
    - 2nd Anniversary Exhibition, (1934) (Reel 5401, Frame 897-901)
    - 3rd Anniversary Exhibition, (1935) (Reel 5401, Frame 902-904)
    - 4th Anniversary Exhibition, (1936) (Reel 5401, Frame 905-907)
    - 5th Anniversary Exhibition, (1937) (Reel 5401, Frame 908-910)
    - 6th Anniversary Exhibition, (1938) (Reel 5401, Frame 911-913)
    - 7th Anniversary Exhibition, (1939) (Reel 5401, Frame 914-918)
    - 8th Anniversary Exhibition, (1940) (Reel 5401, Frame 919-921)
    - 10th Anniversary Exhibition, (1942) (Reel 5401, Frame 922-1017)
    - 12th Anniversary Exhibition, (1944) (Reel 5401, Frame 1018-1021)
    - 13th Anniversary Exhibition, (1945) (Reel 5401, Frame 1022-1024)
    - 14th Anniversary Exhibition, (1946) (Reel 5401, Frame 1025-1027)
    - 19th Anniversary Exhibition, (1951) (Reel 5401, Frame 1028-1030)
    - 25th Anniversary Exhibition, (1957) (Reel 5401, Frame 1033-1047)
    - 26th Anniversary Exhibition, (1958) (Reel 5401, Frame 1048-1050)
    - 27th Anniversary Exhibition, (1959) (Reel 5401, Frame 1051-1057)
    - 28th Anniversary Exhibition, (1960) (Reel 5401, Frame 1058-1060)
    - 29th Anniversary Exhibition, (1961) (Reel 5401, Frame 1061-1064)
    - 30th Anniversary Exhibition, (1962) (Reel 5401, Frame 1065-1191)
    - 39th Anniversary Exhibition, (1971) (Reel 5401, Frame 1192-1194)
    - 40th Anniversary Exhibition, (1972) (Reel 5401, Frame 1195-1204)
    - 50th Anniversary Exhibition, (1982) (Reel 5401, Frame 1205-1274)
    - Art In Interiors, 1952 (Reel 5401, Frame 1275-1285)
    - Art In Interiors, 1953 (Reel 5401, Frame 1286-1477)
    - Art In Interiors, 1954 (Reel 5401, Frame 1478-1479)
    - Art In Interiors, 1955 (Reel 5401, Frame 1480-1484)
    - Art In Interiors, 1956 (Reel 5401, Frame 1485-1488)
    - Art In Interiors, 1957 (Reel 5401, Frame 1489-1500)
    - Art In Interiors, 1958 (Reel 5401, Frame 1501-1514)
    - Art In Interiors, 1959 (Reel 5402, Frame 5-48)
    - Art In Interiors, 1960 (Reel 5402, Frame 49-139)
    - Art In Interiors, 1961 (Reel 5402, Frame 140-217)
    - Art In Interiors, undated (Reel 5402, Frame 218-268)
    - Art to Live With (Abraham & Straus), 1948 (Reel 5402, Frame 373-472)
    - Art: USA: 58 and Art: USA: 59, 1958-1959 (Reel 5402, Frame 289-372)
    - The Ballet, 1978 (Reel 5402, Frame 473-488)
    - Barabbas (traveling show), 1961-1965, undated (Reel 5402, Frame 489-857)
    - Bartle, Annette, 1966. (Reel 5402, Frame 858-865)
    - Berman, Saul, undated (Reel 5402, Frame 866-868)
    - Bishop, Isabel, 1945/1946-1949/1950 (traveling show) (Reel 5402, Frame 869-882)
    - Bishop, Isabel, 1974 (Reel 5402, Frame 883-886)
    - Bishop, Isabel, 1974 (University of Arizona Art Museum) (Reel 5402, Frame 887-1114)
    - Bishop, Isabel, 1975 (Reel 5402, Frame 1115-1119)
    - Bishop, Isabel, 1976 (Reel 5402, Frame 1120-1122)
    - Bishop, Isabel, 1978 (Reel 5402, Frame 1123-1152)
    - Cadmus, Paul, 1945/46-1946/47 (traveling show) (Reel 5402, Frame 1153-1160)
    - Cadmus, Paul, 1968 (Reel 5402, Frame 1161-1217)
    - Cadmus, Paul, 1979 (Reel 5402, Frame 1218-1346)
    - Central Illinois Art Exposition (Bloomington, Ill.), 1939 (Reel 5402, Frame 1347-1821)
    - Central Illinois Art Exposition (Bloomington, Ill.), cont., 1939 (Reel 5403, Frame 5-663)
    - Citron, Minna, undated (Reel 5403, Frame 664-666)
    - Contemporary American Painting (traveling show), undated (Reel 5403, Frame 667-671)
    - Davis, Gladys Rockmore, 1935 (Reel 5403, Frame 672-664)
    - Davis, Gladys Rockmore, (Miami University, Oxford, Ohio), 1955 (Reel 5403, Frame 665-698)
    - Davis, Gladys Rockmore, 1955/1956 (Reel 5403, Frame 699-742)
    - Davis, Gladys Rockmore, 1956 (Reel 5403, Frame 743-757)
    - Dealers Show American Art, 1941 (Reel 5403, Frame 758-840)
    - Development of a Painting (traveling show), 1951/1952-1969/1970 (Reel 5403, Frame 841-1088)
    - Drawings and Prints (traveling show), 1941/1942-1966/1967 (Reel 5403, Frame 1089-1194)
    - Flowers in Art (traveling show), 1941/1942-1966/1967 (Reel 5403, Frame 1195-1246)
    - Freedman, Maurice, 1970 (Reel 5403, Frame 1247-1255)
    - Freedman, Maurice, 1977 (Reel 5403, Frame 1256-1257)
    - Freedman, Maurice, 1979 (Reel 5403, Frame 1258-1302)
    - Good Drawing (traveling show), 1955/1956-1969/1970 (Reel 5403, Frame 1303-1399)
    - Group Shows, 1934/35-1973/74, undated (Reel 5403, Frame 1400-1523)
    - Group Shows, cont. 1934/1935-1973/1974, undated (Reel 5404, Frame 5-32)
    - Hale, Nathan Cabot, 1964 (Reel 5404, Frame 33-38)
    - Hale, Nathan Cabot, 1968 (Reel 5404, Frame 39-54)
    - Kingman, Dong (traveling show), 1945/1946-1950/1951, undated (Reel 5404, Frame 55-68)
    - Koerner, Henry (traveling show, 1946/1947, undated (Reel 5404, Frame 69-73)
    - Large Oil Group (traveling show), 1947/1948-1957/1958 (Reel 5404, Frame 74-133)
    - Magafan, Ethel, 1969 (Reel 5404, Frame 134-149)
    - Magafan, Ethel, 1970/71 (Reel 5404, Frame 150-206)
    - Maine Artists, 1964 (Reel 5404, Frame 207-210)
    - Maine Artists, 1966 (Reel 5404, Frame 211-217)
    - Martin, Fletcher, 1941 (Reel 5404, Frame 218-220)
    - Meyer, Fred, 1968 (Reel 5404, Frame 221-233)
    - Meyer, Fred, 1978 (Reel 5404, Frame 234-242)
    - Michener Foundation Collection, Allentown Art Museum (traveling show), 1962-1964 (Reel 5404, Frame 243-299)
    - Moller, Hans, 1967 (Reel 5404, Frame 300-307)
    - Moller, Hans, 1970 (Reel 5404, Frame 308-315)
    - Moller, Hans, 1979 (Reel 5404, Frame 316-342)
    - Moyer, Roy, 1967 (Reel 5404, Frame 343-382)
    - Nagler, Fred (traveling show), 1947/1948 (Reel 5404, Frame 383-386)
    - Nagler, Fred (traveling show), 1963/1964-1968/1969 (Reel 5404, Frame 387-406)
    - New Talent Festival, 1973 (Reel 5404, Frame 407-491)
    - New Talent Festival, 1974 (Reel 5404, Frame 492-604)
    - New Talent Festival, 1976 (Reel 5404, Frame 605-609)
    - New Talent Festival, 1977 (Reel 5404, Frame 610-664)
    - New York World's Fair, Pavilion of American Interiors, 1964 (Reel 5404, Frame 665-800)
    - Oil Group (traveling show), 1940/1941-1968/1969, undated (Reel 5404, Frame 801-965)
    - Onandoga Silk Co. (traveling show), 1947/1948 (Reel 5404, Frame 969-1183)
    - Paintings and Drawings of the Nude (traveling show), 1952/1953 (Reel 5404, Frame 1184-1187)
    - Pavilion of American Interiors (see: New York World's Fair) (Reel 5404)
    - Peirce, Waldo, 1946/1947-1948/1949 (Reel 5404, Frame 1188-1193)
    - Peirce, Waldo, 1965/1966-1967/1968 (traveling show) (Reel 5404, Frame 1194-1350)
    - Peirce, Waldo, 1972 (Reel 5404, Frame 1351-1357)
    - Peirce, Waldo, 1977 (Reel 5404, Frame 1358-1432)
    - Religion in Contemporary Art (traveling show), 1955/1956-1971/1972 (Reel 5404, Frame 1433-1510)
    - Religion in Contemporary Art (traveling show), cont., 1955/56-1971/72 (Reel 5405, Frame 5-112)
    - Rosenthal, Doris (traveling show), 1944/1945-1947/1948, undated (Reel 5405, Frame 113-128)
    - Self-Portraits, 1981 (Reel 5405, Frame 129-152)
    - Sepeshy, Zoltan (traveling show), 1945/1946-1946/1947 (Reel 5405, Frame 153-158)
    - Small Oil Group (traveling show), 1944/1945-1949/1950 (Reel 5405, Frame 159-179)
    - Small Paintings, 1966 (Reel 5405, Frame 180-182)
    - Smith, Jacob Getlar (traveling show), 1942/1943 (Reel 5405, Frame 183-185)
    - Upjohn Co. Collection (traveling show), 1944-1950, undated (Reel 5405, Frame 186-1522)
    - Watercolor Group [title varies slightly] (traveling show), 1940/1941-1969/1970 (Reel 5406, Frame 5-107)
    - Price Lists, 1942-1976, undated (Reel 5406, Frame 108-261)
- Inventories and Sales Records, 1932-1981, undated, Series 3:; (5.3 linear ft.)
  Inventories (2 linear feet) of Midtown Galleries stock, 1946-1980, and undated, indicate artist, title, date, medium, dimensions, and whether a piece is framed or unframed. Often, a bin number or other location is specified, and occasionally insurance values are included. Most inventories are arranged alphabetically by artist, but some are arranged by storage location; some are in the form of lists and others are card files. Other records relating to gallery stock are included in this series. These include lists of paintings on consignment and lists of paintings returned to artists, as well as loan/shipping logs, and "traffic cards."
  Sales records (3.3 linear feet) include "group totals," artists account ledgers, and copies of sales slips arranged by name of artist.
  3.1: Inventories, 1946-1981, undated
  3.2: Sales, Group Totals and Artist Account Ledgers, 1932-1946, undated
  3.3: Artist Accounts, A-Z, 1932-1979, undated
  - Inventories, 1946-1981, undated, 3.1:
    "Traffic cards," found in this subseries, are 3 x 5 cards arranged alphabetically by artist that indicate title, date, and exhibition history. Inventory cards are 5 X 8 cards arranged alphabetically by artist and indicate title, date, size, value, and exhibition history.
    - Inventory of Paintings at Berkeley Express & Moving Co., 1946-1949, undated (Reel 5406, Frame 262-288)
    - Inventories, A-Z (by artist), 1965-1967 (Reel 5406, Frame 289-386)
    - Inventories, A-Z (by artist), 1970 (Reel 5406, Frame 387-442)
    - Inventories, A-Z (by artist), cont., 1970 (Reel 5406, Frame 495-496)
    - Inventories, A-Z (by artist), cont., 1970 (Reel 5406, Frame 519-540)
    - Inventories, A-Z (by artist), 1972 (Reel 5406, Frame 443-463)
    - Inventories, A-Z (by artist), cont., 1972 (Reel 5406, Frame 501-506)
    - Inventories, A-Z (by artist), 1973 (Reel 5406, Frame 464-494)
    - Inventories, A-Z (by artist), cont., 1973 (Reel 5406, Frame 497-500)
    - Inventories, A-Z (by artist), cont., 1973 (Reel 5406, Frame 507-518)
    - Inventories, A-Z (by artist), cont., 1973 (Reel 5406, Frame 520-538)
    - Inventories, A-Z (by artist), cont., 1973 (Reel 5406, Frame 541-613)
    - Inventories, A-Z (by artist and warehouse location), 1977 (Reel 5406, Frame 614-659)
    - Inventories, A-Z (by artist), 1978 (Reel 5406, Frame 660-681)
    - Inventories, A-Z (by artist), 1979-1980 (Reel 5406, Frame 838-890)
    - Inventories, A-Z (by artist), 1981 (Reel 5406, Frame 891-964)
    - Inventories, A-Z (by artist), undated (Reel 5406, Frame 682-837)
    - Inventories, A-Z (by artist), cont., undated (Reel 5406, Frame 965-1013)
    - Paintings on Consignment, 1935-1952, undated (Reel 5406, Frame 1014-1080)
    - Paintings Returned to Artists (A-Z), 1949 (Reel 5406, Frame 1081-1098)
    - Loan/Shipping Logs, 1937-1950, undated (Reel 5406)
    - "Traffic Cards," circa 1947-1950 (Reel 5407, Frame 64-248)
    - Inventory cards, undated (Reel 5407, Frame 249-1525)
    - Inventory cards, cont., undated (Reel 5408, Frame 5-503)
  - Sales, Group Totals and Artist Account Ledgers, 1932-1946, undated, 3.2:
    - Group Totals, 1945 (Reel 5408, Frame 505-529)
    - Artists Accounts Ledgers, A-Z, 1932-1945 (Reel 5408, Frame 530-624)
    - Artists Accounts Ledgers, A-Z, 1945-1946 (Reel 5408, Frame 625-1081)
    - Artists Accounts Ledgers, A-Z, undated (Reel 5408, Frame 1082-1204)
  - Artist Accounts, A-Z, 1932-1979, undated, 3.3:
    This subseries includes sales slips indicating name and address of buyer, date of sale, artist, title, and price. There are also notes on expenses to be deducted, and the amount and dates of payments to artists.
    - Bartel, Annette, 1957-1966 (Reel 5409, Frame 5-71)
    - Belle, Cecile, 1953-1964 (Reel 5409, Frame 72-91)
    - Betts, Edward, 1960-1978 (Reel 5409, Frame 92-219)
    - Betts, Edward, cont., 1960-1978 (Reel 5409, Frame 382-384)
    - Billings, Henry, 1950-1963 (Reel 5409, Frame 220-235)
    - Binford, Julien, 1944-1974 (Reel 5409, Frame 236-381)
    - Binford, Julien, cont., 1944-1974 (Reel 5409, Frame 385-400)
    - Bishop, Isabel, 1932-1976 (Reel 5409, Frame 401-1315)
    - Cadmus, Paul, 1937-1974 (Reel 5409, Frame 1316-1526)
    - Cadmus, Paul, cont., 1937-1974 (Reel 5410, Frame 5-1156)
    - Coiner, Charles, 1961-1974 (Reel 5410, Frame 1157-1319)
    - Crawford, Alice Berle, 1974 (Reel 5410, Frame 1320-1328)
    - Davis, Gladys Rockmore, 1942-1957, undated (Reel 5410, Frame 1329-1526)
    - Davis, Gladys Rockmore, cont., 1942-1957, undated (Reel 5411, Frame 5-95)
    - Etnier, Stephen, 1967-1974 (Reel 5411, Frame 96-189)
    - Etting, Emlen, 1944-1966 (Reel 5411, Frame 190-354)
    - Fiene, Ernest, 1958-1966 (Reel 5411, Frame 355-421)
    - Freedman, Maurice, 1944-1975 (Reel 5411, Frame 422-522)
    - Hale, Nathan, 1963-1969 (Reel 5411, Frame 523-666)
    - Kester, Lenard, 1947-1952 (Reel 5411, Frame 667-700)
    - Kingman, Dong, 1954-1965 (Reel 5411, Frame 701-890)
    - Koerner, Henry, 1947-1952 (Reel 5411, Frame 891-1100)
    - Magafan, Ethel, 1968-1975 (Reel 5411, Frame 1101-1171)
    - Meyer, Fred, 1947-1975 (Reel 5411, Frame 1172-1313)
    - Moller, Hans, 1964-1976 (Reel 5411, Frame 1314-1506)
    - Moyer, Roy, 1965-1974 (Reel 5411, Frame 1507-1535)
    - Moyer, Roy, cont., 1965-1974 (Reel 5412, Frame 2-85)
    - Nagler, Fred, 1939-1954 (Reel 5412, Frame 86-139)
    - Palmer, William C., 1940-1974 (Reel 5412, Frame 140-810)
    - Parsons, Betty, 1945-1955 (Reel 5412, Frame 811-842)
    - Peirce, Waldo, 1935-1973 (Reel 5412, Frame 843-1215)
    - Puccinelli, Raymond, 1959-1965 (Reel 5412, Frame 1216-1247)
    - Reinhardt, Siegfried, 1960-1971 (Reel 5412, Frame 1248-1347)
    - Rosenthal, Doris, 1943-1973 (Reel 5412, Frame 1348-1532)
    - Rosenthal, Doris, cont., 1943-1973 (Reel 5413, Frame 5-47)
    - Saarinen, Lilian, 1944-1956 (Reel 5413, Frame 48-63)
    - Schoener, Jason, 1957-1979 (Reel 5413, Frame 64-351)
    - Sepeshy, Zoltan, 1932-1973 (Reel 5413, Frame 352-536)
    - Shulkin, Anatol, 1938-1961 (Reel 5413, Frame 537-560)
    - Sivard, Robert, 1952-1977 (Reel 5413, Frame 561-579)
    - Soyer, Isaac, 1939-1950 (Reel 5413, Frame 580-601)
    - Thon, William, 1943-1978 (Reel 5413, Frame 602-1477)
    - Varga, Margit, 1939-1974 (Reel 5413, Frame 1478-1529)
    - Vickrey, Robert, 1953-1974 (Reel 5414, Frame 1-1099)
    - Vickrey, Robert, cont., 1953-1974 (Reel 5415, Frame 5-75)
- Financial Records, 1933-1957, Series 4:; (3.5 linear feet)
  Financial records consist of invoices for bills paid (arranged alphabetically by name of creditor); banking records such as statements and passbooks; accounting records including an accounts receivable ledger and a petty cash book; and federal, state, and city income and business tax records. Because these are likely to be of interest to a very limited number of researchers, this series was not microfilmed; of course, arrangements may be made for the original records to be consulted at our Washington office. Financial information concerning gallery stock is included in Series 3: Inventory and Sales Records, and letters relating to gallery purchases and sales may also be included with Series 1: Administrative Correspondence.
  - Bills Paid, 1937-1957 (Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
  - Banking Records, 1935-1955 (Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
  - Accounting Records, 1933-1938 (Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
  - Tax Returns and Related Records, 1935-1955 (Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
- Miscellaneous, 1934-1985, undated, Series 5:; (2 linear feet)
  Miscellaneous records include Midtown Galleries guest registers complete at 32 volumes except for the first two years of the galleries's existence. This series includes artifacts, mainly samples of artist-designed or inspired silk fabrics produced for the Onandoga Silk Co.; several department stores featured garments made from the fabrics and mounted small exhibitions of the paintings on which the fabrics were based. Also, two brass labels from paintings and a sound recording with a cover designed by a Midtown Galleries artist. Writings by authors other than Alan D. Gruskin are manuscripts about Isabel Bishop and Philip Guston (Gruskin's writings are part of Series 8: Personal Papers of Alan D. and Mary J. Gruskin). Legal documents include items such as the galleries' Act of Incorporation, partnership agreements, and leases.
  - Guest Registers, 1934-1937 (Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
  - Guest Registers, "through 1951," [1938-1951] (Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
  - Guest Registers, 1952-1985 (Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
  - Guest Registers, undated (Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
  - Artifacts, Artist-Designed Fabrics, Onandoga Silk Co., 1946-1947, (15 samples) (Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
    - Unidentified (2) (Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
    - Binford, Julien, The Farmer's Daughter (Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
    - Binford, Julien, White Chickens (Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
    - Binford, Julien, Woman with a Hat (Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
    - Davis, Gladys Rockmore, Ballet Slippers (Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
    - Davis, Gladys Rockmore, Children at Play (Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
    - Davis, Gladys Rockmore, Giselle (Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
    - Kingman, Dong, Chickens in Square (Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
    - Kingman, Dong, New Orleans (Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
    - Kingman, Dong, Red Poppies (Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
    - Palmer, William, Horses (Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
    - Peirce, Waldo, Fish in Net (Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
    - Peirce, Waldo, Sea Fantasy (Reel unfilmed, Frame unfilmed)
- Photographs, circa 1925-circa 1980, Series 6:; (6.5 linear feet)
  This series is organized into five subseries:
  6.1: People, A-Z and Unidentified
  6.2: Works of Art, A-Z
  6.3: Exhibitions, A-Z and Unidentified, 1939-1972, undated
  6.4: Miscellaneous, A-Z, 1943-1969, undated
  6.5: Negatives
  - People, A-Z and Unidentified, 6.1:
    People includes artists, most but not all were associated with Midtown Galleries; also, photographs of Alan D. and Mary J. Gruskin. Photographs of people are arranged alphabetically by name, followed by unidentified individuals.
    - Anderson, Karl (Reel 5415, Frame 256-259)
    - Belle, Cecile (Reel 5415, Frame 260-265)
    - Betts, Edward (Reel 5415, Frame 266-276)
    - Billings, Henry (Reel 5415, Frame 277-285)
    - Binford, Julien (Reel 5415, Frame 286-300)
    - Bishop, Isabel (Reel 5415, Frame 301-304)
    - Cadmus, Paul (Reel 5415, Frame 305-308)
    - Coiner, Charles (Reel 5415, Frame 309-316)
    - Custer, Bernardine (Reel 5415, Frame 317-320)
    - Davis, Gladys Rockmore (Reel 5415, Frame 321-345)
    - Dealers Installing Exhibition, Dealers Show American Art, 1941 (Reel 5415, Frame 346-359)
    - Etting, Emlen (Reel 5415, Frame 360-375)
    - Evergood, Philip (Reel 5415, Frame 376-379)
    - Fiene, Ernest (Reel 5415, Frame 380-392)
    - Freedman, Maurice (Reel 5415, Frame 393-397)
    - Gerald, John (Reel 5415, Frame 398-401)
    - Godowsky, Gordon (Reel 5415, Frame 402-405)
    - Gruskin, Alan D. (Reel 5415, Frame 406-423)
    - Gruskin, Alan D., with Artists (Reel 5415, Frame 424-449)
    - Gruskin, Alan D., with Friends (Reel 5437, Frame 349-384)
    - Gruskin, Alan D. and Mary Gruskin (Reel 5437, Frame 450-455)
    - Gruskin, Alan D. and Mary Gruskin, cont. (Reel 5437, Frame 328-348)
    - Gruskin, Mary (Reel 5415, Frame 456-461)
    - Gruskin, Mary, with Artists (Reel 5415, Frame 462-465)
    - Gruskin, Mary, with Others (Reel 5415, Frame 466-469)
    - Hale, Nathan Cabot (Reel 5415, Frame 470-485)
    - Harkavy, Minna (Reel 5415, Frame 486-491)
    - Healey, Francis C. (Reel 5415, Frame 492-494)
    - Karfiol, Bernard (Reel 5415, Frame 495-498)
    - Kerkam, Earl (Reel 5415, Frame 499-502)
    - Kingman, Dong (Reel 5415, Frame 503-639)
    - Koch, John (Reel 5415, Frame 640-643)
    - Koerner, Henry (Reel 5415, Frame 644-653)
    - Lahm, Reneé (Reel 5415, Frame 656-659)
    - Magafan, Ethel (Reel 5415, Frame 660-666)
    - Maldarelli, Oronzio (Reel 5415, Frame 667-697)
    - Martin, Fletcher (Reel 5415, Frame 698-708)
    - Mayhew, Richard (Reel 5415, Frame 709-712)
    - McCobb, John (Reel 5415, Frame 713-716)
    - Mechau, Frank (Reel 5415, Frame 717-725)
    - Meltsner, Paul (Reel 5415, Frame 726-731)
    - Meyer, Fred (Reel 5415, Frame 732-738)
    - Nagler, Fred (Reel 5415, Frame 739-742)
    - Pach, Walter (Reel 5415, Frame 743-748)
    - Pahlmann, William (Reel 5415, Frame 749-753)
    - Palmer, William (Reel 5415, Frame 754-775)
    - Peirce, Alzira (Reel 5415, Frame 776-791)
    - Peirce, Waldo (Reel 5415, Frame 792-811)
    - Prestopino, Gregorio (Reel 5415, Frame 812-816)
    - Reinhardt, Siegfried (Reel 5415, Frame 817-822)
    - Rosenthal, Doris (Reel 5415, Frame 823-874)
    - Saarinen, Lilian Swann (Reel 5415, Frame 875-887)
    - Schoener, Jason (Reel 5415, Frame 888-893)
    - Sepeshy, Zoltan (Reel 5415, Frame 894-900)
    - Shrallow, Fred (Reel 5415, Frame 901-904)
    - Shulkin, Anatol (Reel 5415, Frame 905-912)
    - Simkhovitch, Simka (Reel 5415, Frame 913-915)
    - Sivard, Robert (Reel 5415, Frame 916-919)
    - Sokole, Miron (Reel 5415, Frame 920-923)
    - Soyer, Isaac (Reel 5415, Frame 924-931)
    - Taubes, Frederic (Reel 5415, Frame 932-941)
    - Teague, Walter Dorwin (Reel 5415, Frame 942-945)
    - Thon, William (Reel 5415, Frame 946-1006)
    - Upjohn Co. Officials (Allen, Gilmore, Morris, Patterson, E.G. and L. N. Upjohn) (Reel 5415, Frame 1007-1022)
    - Varga, Margit (Reel 5415, Frame 1023-1039)
    - Vickrey, Robert (Reel 5415, Frame 1040-1050)
    - Wingate, Arline (Reel 5415, Frame 1051-1058)
    - Wisner, John B. (Reel 5415, Frame 1059-1062)
    - Unidentified (Reel 5415, Frame 1063-1066)
  - Works of Art, A-Z, 6.2:
    Photographs of works of art are arranged by name of artist and photographs of exhibitions are arranged alphabetically by exhibition title.
    - Adler, M. H. (Reel 5415, Frame 1068-1070)
    - Alan, S. (Reel 5415, Frame 1071-1073)
    - Aldrich, M. Azzi (Reel 5416, Frame 5-154)
    - Armistead, Horace (Reel 5416, Frame 155-168)
    - Barnett, Herbert (Reel 5416, Frame 169-173)
    - Baum, Mark (Reel 5416, Frame 174-176)
    - Bell, Enid (Reel 5416, Frame 177-180)
    - Belle, Cecile (Reel 5416, Frame 181-348)
    - Berman, Saul (see: Saul) (Reel 5416)
    - Betts, Edward (Reel 5416, Frame 349-352)
    - Billings, Henry (Reel 5416, Frame 353-415)
    - Binford, Julien (Reel 5416, Frame 416-442)
    - Blume, Peter (Reel 5416, Frame 443-446)
    - Bonnard, Pierre (Reel 5416, Frame 447-450)
    - Boss, Homer (Reel 5416, Frame 451-462)
    - Bowden, Priscilla (Reel 5416, Frame 463-466)
    - Bradshaw, Glenn (Reel 5416, Frame 467-476)
    - Breinin, Raymond (Reel 5416, Frame 477-489)
    - Buckley, Mary (Reel 5416, Frame 481-484)
    - Burchfield, Charles (Reel 5416, Frame 485-488)
    - Cadmus, Paul (Reel 5416, Frame 489-492)
    - Campbell, A. (Reel 5416, Frame 493-503)
    - Cézanne, Paul (Reel 5416, Frame 504-508)
    - Church, Frederick S. (Reel 5416, Frame 509-512)
    - Citron, Minna (Reel 5416, Frame 513-554)
    - Clemens, Paul (Reel 5416, Frame 555-677)
    - Coiner, Charles (Reel 5416, Frame 678-681)
    - Cook, Howard (Reel 5416, Frame 682-685)